sugardoodle.net 2017-06-08

# Privacy Policy - T's & C's

Print Email Details
     Written by Sugardoodle.net 
     Published: 22 December 2007 

####   
Sugardoodle.net - Privacy Policy - Terms & Conditions

At  Sugardoodle.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.  Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Sugardoodle.net, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

######  **Personal Information**

The only personal information we collect is what you voluntarily create an account on Sugardoodle.

######  **Privacy**

Users who become a fan of Sugardoodle on facebook or create an account on Sugardoodle.net will occassionaly receive emails from Sugardoodle.  Facebook fans will also receive status updates and posts.

######  **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

######  **Cookies**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as bookmarks, commenting and content submission.

We also use third party advertisements on Sugardoodle.net to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative **  at ** **[www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)** **.**

fulltext
